Coming into palming her arm and this is the one the side poses.
So first thing I want to do is get her on her side.
Pillow about middle of the hip right here, move your hand in the garment just a little bit so you'd be comfortable, grab a hold of the back of the leg, gently twist her over and we want her to come all the way on to her side.
Oh, her neck looks very uncomfortable.
So what we're going to do, ask her to lift her head, place something underneath the head, a blanket, a pillow, anything that you've got to help your client feel comfortable.
I'm going to come in to a nice kneeling diamond here and I'm rarely leaning into her, give her a little bit of control, lengthening that arm.
Now if you've got someone that's really, really tiny and you got a nice little gap right here, you want to place a pillow or blanket right there too to keep your client comfortable.
I want to start right here towards the elbows, gently press down with the palm and work it way up.
You can give about three times.
Start right back towards the elbow and again, palming.
And I'm not, what I'm kind of doing is pressing down, down, down, give her a little stretch and still leaning against her slightly, keep that connection and again palming towards the middle, out, out.
Here, walk it out and literally hand to the wrist, hand to the shoulder, lengthen that arm.
Perfect.